[{
    "question": "When does India celebrate Independence Day?",
	"options": ["A. 15th August", 
		"B. 2nd October", 
		"C. 26th January", 
		"D. 4th July"],
	"answer": "A. 15th August"
},
{
    "question": "Nobel prize is awarded for which of the following disciplines?",
	"options": ["A. Literature, peace and economics", 
		"B. Medicine or Physiology", 
		"C. Chemistry and Physics", 
		"D. All the above"],
	"answer": "D. All the above"
},
{
    "question": "'LIBRA' an alternative of existing cryptocurrency like bitcoin is being developed by?",
	"options": ["A. Facebook", 
		"B. Google", 
		"C. Microsoft", 
		"D. None of the above"],
	"answer": "A. Facebook"
},
{
    "question": "Headquater of International Olympic Committee is situated at?",
	"options": ["A. Athens", 
		"B. Lausanne", 
		"C. Dubai", 
		"D. None of the above"],
	"answer": "B. Lausanne"
},
{
    "question": "'The Coalition Years' is the autobiography of?",
	"options": ["A. L.K Advani", 
		"B. Pranab Mukherjee", 
		"C. Atal Behari Vajpayee", 
		"D. Sonia Gandhi"],
	"answer": "B. Pranab Mukherjee"
},
{
    "question": "Entomology studies what?",
	"options": ["A. Behavior of human beings",
		"B. Insects",
		"C. The origin and history of technical and scientific terms",
		"D. The formation of rocks"],
	"answer": "B. Insects"
},
{
    "question": "Galileo was an astronomer who",
	"options": ["A. Developed the telescope",
		"B. Discovered four satellites of Jupiter",
		"C. discovered that the movement of pendulum produces a regular time measurement",
		"D. All the above"],
	"answer": "B. Discovered four satellites of Jupiter"
},
{
    "question": "Who is the father of geometry?",
	"options": ["A. Aristotle",
		"B. Euclid",
		"C. Pythagoras",
		"D. Kepler"],
	"answer": "B. Euclid"
},
{
    "question": "Which is the first search engine of the internet?",
	"options": ["A. Yahoo",
		"B. Wais",
		"C. Archie",
		"D. Mozilla"],
	"answer": "C. Archie"
},
{
    "question": "In a Database Management System(DBMS) the content and the location of data is identified by ?",
	"options": ["A. Subdata",
		"B. Sequence Data",
		"C. Beta Data",
		"D. Meta Data"],
	"answer": "D. Meta Data"
}]